nba-2k.com 2013-06-04

# Privacy - NBASky.COM - NBA 2K13 Patches, NBA 2K13 Rosters

## Privacy

When you visit the NBASKY.COM web site ("http://nbasky.com/"), we want you to be assured that we make every effort to respect your personal and financial privacy. We will only use the information that we collect about you lawfully (in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998).

The purpose of this policy is to inform you on every aspect of data gathering, why we do it, how we do it and then what we do with it.

 **Privacy Notice**

This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for (NBASKY.COM). This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this web site. It will notify you of the following:

  1. What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the web site, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.
  2. What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.
  3. The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.
  4. How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.

 **Data Gathering Key Points**

 **1\. Ownership of Information**

We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from that disclosed in this statement. The products we sell will require clients details for license information. Please contact the respective software producer if you wish to review their privacy policy.

 **2\. Users 16 and under**

If you are aged 16 or under, please get your parent/guardian's permission beforehand whenever you provide personal information to the KiKi website. Users without this consent are not allowed to provide us with personal information.

 **3\. Use of Cookies**

Cookies are pieces of data stored on your hard drive concerning a current or previous web experience, such as a username/password combination used to gain access to some areas of the site or other services. We may use a cookie to record previously established interests and preferences (via data submitted to us) so as to enhance the experience whilst using our site. Because the cookie is client side, i.e. on your hard drive, your privacy is in no way compromised.

You may deactivate cookies in your web browser, or reject the creation of a cookie depending on your personal preferences. If you do so then our web site functionality may be compromised and certain services may not be available.

 **5\. IP Address Information**

Each time you access information then we record what you access and the IP address you use to access the data. An IP address is a unique identifier given to you by your Internet provider when you connect to the Internet. This may differ each time you connect or be permanently assigned depending on your arrangements. We use these addresses to track your movements, analyse broad trends such a geographical location and by such improve our quality of service.

IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. We shall also store your browser version to detect tends on what browsers people perfer. We may from time to time share information gathered in this way with our partners. This information is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person.

 **6\. Links to Other Sites**

This web site may contain links to other sites. KiKi cannot be held responsible for the privacy practices of other such sites. Please do not assume that other sites abide by our privacy standards.

 **7\. Security of Collected Data**

KiKi takes every sensible precaution to protect the information we collect from our users. Access to this information is protected both online and off-line. KiKi does not store any financial information of customers and any off-line transactions.

 **8\. Site and Service Updates**

We may use information collected to periodically send our users announcements and product updates via e-mail.

 **9\. How to find and control your cookies**

 _If you're using Netscape 6.0:_

On your Task Bar, click:

1\. Edit, then

2\. Preferences

3\. Click on Advanced

4\. Click on Cookies

 _If you're using Internet Explorer 6.0:_

1\. Choose Tools, then

2\. Internet Options

3\. Click the Privacy Tab

4\. Click on Custom Level

5\. Click on the 'Advanced' button

6\. Check the 'override automatic cookie handing' box and select Accept, Block or Prompt for action as appropriate.

 _If you're using Internet Explorer 5.0 or 5.5:_

1\. Choose Tools, then

2\. Internet Options

3\. Click the Security tab

4\. Click on Custom Level

5\. Scroll down to the sixth option to see how cookies are handled by IE5 and change to Accept, Disable, or Prompt for action as appropriate.

 _If you're using Internet Explorer 4.0:_

1\. Choose View, then

2\. Internet Options

3\. Click the Advanced tab

4\. Scroll down to the yellow exclamation icon under Security and choose one of the three options to regulate your use of cookies.

 _If you're using Internet Explorer 3.0:_

You can View, Options, Advanced, then click on the button that says Warn before Accepting Cookies.

 _If you're using Netscape Communicator 4.0:_

On your Task Bar, click:

1\. Edit, then

2\. Preferences

3\. Click on Advanced

4\. Set your options in the box that says Cookies

 **Information Collection, Use, and Sharing**

We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.

We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order.

Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.

 **Your Access to and Control Over Information**

You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website:

  * See what data we have about you, if any.
  * Change/correct any data we have about you.
  * Have us delete any data we have about you.
  * Express any concern you have about our use of your data.

 **Security**

We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.

We only correct your cookies for visiting our website (mostly for commentors)

 **If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via email nba [at] fan [dot] com.**
